<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<note>
  <name>It's Okay Not To Be Okay</name>
  <year>2020 | 13+ | 1 Season</year>
  <title>An extraordinary road to emotional healing opens up for an antisocial children's book writer and a selfless psych ward caretaker when they cross paths.</title>
  
  <data1>It's Okay to Not Be Okay (Korean: 사이코지만 괜찮아; RR: Saikojiman Gwaenchana; lit. Psycho But It's Okay) is a South Korean romance drama television series written by Jo Yong and directed by Park Shin-woo. It stars Kim Soo-hyun, Seo Yea-ji, Oh Jung-se and Park Gyu-young. The series follows a selfless psych ward caretaker and an antisocial children's book writer. The series was broadcast for 16 episodes on tvN and Netflix from June 20, 2020, to August 9, 2020. According to Nielsen Korea, it recorded an average nationwide TV viewership rating of 5.4%. It was the most popular show of 2020 in the romance genre on Netflix in South Korea. The New York Times named It's Okay to Not Be Okay one of "The Best International Shows of 2020". Critical responses were primarily positive; some commentators criticized the writing in the latter half of the series but praised the acting by the cast.</data1>
  <data2>Moon Gang-tae (Kim Soo-hyun) lives with his older brother Moon Sang-tae (Oh Jung-se) who has autism. They frequently move from town to town ever since Sang-tae witnessed their mother's murder. Gang-Tae works as a caretaker in a psychiatric ward at every place they settle in. While working in a hospital, he meets a famous children's book writer, Ko Moon-young (Seo Yea-ji), who is rumored to have antisocial personality disorder. Circumstances lead Gang-tae to work at the OK Psychiatric Hospital in Seongjin City, the same city where they all lived when they were young. Meanwhile, Moon-young forms a romantic obsession for Gang-tae after finding out that their pasts overlap. She follows him to Seongjin, where the trio (including Sang-tae) slowly begins to heal each other's emotional wounds. They unravel many secrets, seek comfort from each other and move forward in their lives.</data2>
  <imdb>8.7/10</imdb>

</note>